AMRIT KHAREL

M: 0451279032 E: amrit.kharel6@gmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A graduate student who loves to learn and explore new ideas and concept. Able to adapt and work cooperatively to enhance workflow. An amusing, honest, and charismatic person who enjoys group work and new challenges. Always kept me busy with some project or followed an online tutorial to enhance my skill and build my experience. With all this skill and experience accumulated over the years, I would like to utilise them in your workplace and take opportunities to learn and grow together with your business.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology

2018 - 2020

Majoring in Mobile Computing
Sub-major in Social Media Analytic & Networking

WORK EXPERIENCE

Notebook Solution 2017 - 2017 Alphazone Computers 2018 - 2018

- Dealing with customer service issues such as queries and complaints.
- Troubleshooting customer's PC and solving the problems.
- Performed backup, installing software and fix hardware issues.
- Support customers with technology services and digital access to information supplied
- Troubleshoot base technical issues with end-user hardware, software, and services
- Catalogue and inventory management of ICT equipment
- Assist vendor relations for ICT needs
- Visit onsite and fulfil customers needs for ICT enquires.
- Installing, configuring, and troubleshooting Windows, Linux and MAC.

Toll Customised Solutions, Ingleburn, NSW 2565 2018 - 2019 DHL, Eastern creek, NSW 2766 2019 - 2019 Australian Brush ware 2020 - Present

- Completes shipments by processing and loading orders.
- Prepares orders by processing requests and supply orders; pulling materials; packing boxes; placing orders in the delivery area.
- Provides quality service by following organisation standards.
- Preserves a safe and clean work environment by keeping shelves, pallet area, and workstations neat.
- Promotes clean shipping supply area by complying with procedures, rules, and regulations.
- Completes reports by entering the required information.
- Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.

TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

Communication - Responsible for the conduction of stock replenishment in groups of team members and assisting customers at Filled with Fruits, Notebook Solution and Warehouses. Practical public relation skills through strong communication when dealing with customers. In contrast, exchanging emails on matters of communication and updating information.

Teamwork - I liaised with Macarthur Regional Nepalese Community in organising and attending events and fundraisers, and by facilitating and participating in community and university events. Enhanced teamwork skills in Group Project in University and workplace. This project enabled me to work as part of a team to find solutions and utilise collaborative decision-making skills.

Problem Solving - Working on the project and working on a side project during my free time allowed me to carefully construct where the problem is generated and how to tackle them best. Able to debug and find the solution in a reasonable time. While working under no supervision, I read the environment and tried various solutions to achieve the desired solution.

Time Management and Organisation Skills - Organised successful Nepalese Dashain program, New year, and other programs with Nepalese society members. I also had to organise time between meetings, university work, and personal commitments. Together with one other team member, replenished three aisles of stock in a four-hour shift: well above the average of two aisles.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Mobile Computing

- Competent using programming skills such as Java and swift.
- Worked with multiple APIs, used Firebase and AWS for data storage.
- Build small functional apps based on online materials.

Networking

- Good understanding of Computer Network, cabling, subnetting, Router/Switch configuration and Servers.
- Familiar with Network and Computer Security.
- Understanding of OSI models, internet architecture and networking protocols.
- Web Development
- Competent using programming skills such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and XML
- A competent using database such as MySQL, SQL Server, SQLite, and MongoDB.
- Competent managing user access level and securities in DBMS.
- Competent using ASP.NET CORE
- Able to work at the front end and back end. I worked with APIs, hosted my own Web Server using Lamp Stack, Hosted Web app in Google Cloud, and a good understanding of cloud computing, also a Linux user for over a year.

Data Analyst

- Competent using programming skills such as Python and R
- Experience in anaconda environment and R studio
- Used Google API, Twitter API
- Used various libraries, worked with Big Data and statistics, and have some understanding of predictive models.

Programming and General ICT

- A user of All three primary OS: Window, Linux, and Mac OS
- Knowledge of Computer Hardware and its components.
- Extensive Knowledge in Microsoft Office.
- Competent using programming languages such as C/C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, Python, XML, JSON, R and Swift
- Understanding of Algorithms, Data Structures and Operating System programming
- Used GitHub as version controls and bash shell in Linux environment.

PROFILES

GitHub: https://github.com/amrit06

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/amrit-kharel-3a23331b5/

REFERENCE

Available on request